Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
- Box: 105, Folder: 20 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: What Shell Means to You, Publication (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Program for Security, Publication (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Employee Training Manual, Publication (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: Conference Outline- What Makes People Tick, Publication (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Shell Oil Co. Letter to University of Chicago Librarian, Publication (Box 105, Folder 20)
    April 25, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Opportunity with Shell, Publication (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: Shell News, Publication (Box 105, Folder 20)
    December 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Chicago Division: Hi-Lites Vol. 4 No. 6, Publication (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: Shell Chemical Company: The Houston Plant, Publication (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Item 12: Shell News, Publication (Box 105, Folder 20)
- Box: 105, Folder: 21 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Program for Security, Publication (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Opportunity with Shell, Publication (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Conference Outline- What Makes People Tick, Publication (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Conference Outline: What Makes People Tick, The Behavior Pattern, Publication (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: If You Get Sick, Publication (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Shell Provident Fund Designation of Beneficiary: Supplement to Program for Security, Publication (Box 105, Folder 21)
    January, 1950. Item is in English.
- Box: 105, Folder: 22 (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Pete is a Prime Mover, Publication (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Employee Training Manual, Publication (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Conference Outline- Disability Benefit Plan and Income Protection Insurance, Publication (Box 105, Folder 22)
- Box: 105, Folder: 23 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: 1: What Shell Means to You, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: 2: Your Retirement Program, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: 3:Your Hospital Surgical Medical Benefits Shell HSM Program, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: 4: Your Income Protection and Survivor Benefits, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: 5: Shell Employee Stock Ownership Plan, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: Shell Employee Stock Ownership Plan (SESOP), Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: Shell Dental Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: Shell Oil Co. Interoffice Memorandum, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
    March 26, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Employee Retirement Income Security Act: Erisa Information, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: Shell Oil Co. Letter to Head Office Employees-Houston and Field Locations, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
    December 28, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Shell Oil Co.Letter to All Head Office Employees Outside California, Hawaii, New Jersey and New York, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
    March 20, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Letter to Head Office Managers, Houston, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
    April 10, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Summary of the Shell Employee Stock Ownership Plan, Publication (Box 105, Folder 23)
- Box: 105, Folder: 24 (Box 105, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Shell and Your Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 105, Folder 24)
- Box: 105, Folder: 25 (Box 105, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Shipbuilding Council of America By-Laws, Publication (Box 105, Folder 25)
    May 1939-June 17, 1946. Item is in English.
- Box: 105, Folder: 26 (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 105, Folder 26)
    November 1, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employees' Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 105, Folder 26)
- Box: 105, Folder: 27 (Box 105, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Simmons Company Group Life Insurance Policy, Publication (Box 105, Folder 27)
- Box: 105, Folder: 28 (Box 105, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: An Outline of the Pension Plan of Simmons Manufacturing Company, Publication (Box 105, Folder 28)
- Box: 105, Folder: 29 (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan for Wage Employees (Phiadelphia Plant), Publication (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan for Salary Employees (Phiadelphia Plant), Publication (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: SKF Group Annuity Plan, Publication (Box 105, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: SKF Develops Better Supervisory Teamwork, Publication (Box 105, Folder 29)
    By Harry F. Gracey. August 25, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 106, Folder: 1 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Socialism Today: A Reply to Time Magazine, Publication (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: New York Labor News, Publication (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Box: 106, Folder: 2 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Society for the Advancement of Management: What it is-What it does, Publication (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Society for the Advancement of Management: Work Simplification as a Tool of Top Management, Publication (Box 106, Folder 2)
    By Don F. Copell. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A. G. Bush Library-The University of Chicago: An Approach to Labor Relations, Publication (Box 106, Folder 2)
    By Malcolm L. Denise. March 21, 1963. Item is in English.
- Box: 106, Folder: 3 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: So--You're Thinking About Firing Somebody!, Publication (Box 106, Folder 3)
    By R. G. Beers. July, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Executive Development in Action: Patterns andTechniques, Publication (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Box: 106, Folder: 4 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Society for the Study of Labour History: Bulletin, Publication (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Society for the Study of Labour History: Bulletin, Publication (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Box: 106, Folder: 5 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 4 No. 4, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    December 1976-January 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 3 No. 3, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    July-August 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 4 No. 3, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    September-November 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 4 No. 1, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    March-April 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 4 No. 2, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    May-August 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 3 No. 5, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    November-December 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 5 No. 1, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    April-May 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: SFLRP Blue Ribbon Committee Recommendations, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Treasurer's Report, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    January 1-December 31, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 5 No. 2, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    June-July 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 5 No. 3, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    August-September 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 5 No. 4, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    October-November 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 7 No. 3, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    August-September 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 6 No. 1, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    Spring 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 6 No. 2,3, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    Summer-Fall 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 7 No. 2, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    June-July 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 7 No. 1, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
    April-May 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Newsletter: Society for the Study of Labour History Vol. 7 No. 4, Publication (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Box: 106, Folder: 6 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Tutor Vol. 4 No. 7, Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
    Spring 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Economic Significance of Technological Progress, Publication (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Box: 106, Folder: 7 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: History of The Society of Professional Chemists and Engineers Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Box: 106, Folder: 8 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Antitrust and Bigness: Time to Speak Up, Publication (Box 106, Folder 8)
    By John J. Scott. June 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Conference Type Meetins: A Guide for Those who Plan to Conduct Them, Publication (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Mobil: Health Service, Publication (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: A Guide for Medical Examiners, Publication (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Socony-Mobile Oil Co., Inc. Medical Policy, Publication (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Job Evaluation Manual, Publication (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Box: 106, Folder: 9 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Socony-Vacuum Suggestion System Newsletter Vol. 2 No. 3, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    March, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, Inc., Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    June, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The New Suggestion System Installation and Administration, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Industrial Relations Policy of Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, Incorporated, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, Inc. Vacation Plan for Domestic U.S.A., Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, Inc. 1948 Plan for Employees in Military Training and Service, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    Effective September 1, 1948 and Revised August 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, Inc. Application for Refund: Educational Refund Plan, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Socony-Vacuum Oil Company iNc, Organizational Chart: Industrial Relations Department, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    February 1, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: About Your Job in Eastern Marketing Division, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: The Blue Cross Hospital Plan and the Blue Shield Surgical Plan for Our Employees, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Plan for Employees in Military Service, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    Effective December 7, 1941, Revised October 19, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: A Little Thought may Lead to a BIG Change in Methods, Machines, Materials, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    April 25, 1949, poster. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: FIRE!, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    Poster, May 9, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: So you want a Better Job, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    By Paul W. Boynton. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: So you want a Better Job, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: There's no Mstery About the Source of Successful Suggestions:Your job and the cconditions you know best, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    April 11, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: IDEAS make the difference, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    March 28, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Survey of Pre-Retirement Practices, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
    October 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The New Suggestion System Installation and Administration, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Item 20: Article X. Holidays and Vacations, Publication (Box 106, Folder 9)
- Box: 106, Folder: 10 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Plan for Sickness and accident Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
    Effective September 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Plan for Adjustment of Pensions, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Summary of the 1940 Plan for Annuities and Insurance and Plan for Minimum Retirement Income, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
    Amended September 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Survivorship Benefit Plan for 20-Year Employees, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
    Effective July 1, 1937 and Amended September 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Plan for Termination Allowances, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Plan for Social Security Adjustment Benefits, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Plan for Total and Permanent Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Agreement Between Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, Inc. and Employees Association for Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
    Effective August 6, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Fundamentals of Petroleum Chemistry, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Tips on Talking, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: The Development of People for Key Positions: Domestic Marketing Department, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Review of Performance: Industrial Salesmen, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: JobEvaluation Manual, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Suggestion System: Information for Management, Publication (Box 106, Folder 10)
- Box: 106, Folder: 11 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Americanization: A Discussion of Present Conditions with Recommendations for the Teaching of Non-Americans, Publication (Box 106, Folder 11)
    By Chris H. Paull. Item is in English.
- Box: 106, Folder: 12 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Excerptsof Speech Delivered at the 179th Dinner Meeting of the Economic Club of Chicago: "What is the Difference Between the Japanese Management and the American?", Publication (Box 106, Folder 12)
    By Akio Morita. February 17, 1972. Item is in English.
- Box: 106, Folder: 13 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: By-Laws of the South Jersey Manufacturers' Association, Publication (Box 106, Folder 13)
- Box: 106, Folder: 14 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation Plan: Supervisory, Technical and Office Occupations, Publication (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Job Evaluation: Shop Occupations, Publication (Box 106, Folder 14)
- Box: 106, Folder: 15 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Summary of Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Training and Development catalog, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
    January-December 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Southern California Edison Service Territory Map & Industrial Map of the Los Angeles Five County Area, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Edison News, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
    June 8, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Performance Appraisal and Development Guide, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Employee Qualification Report, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: The Challenge, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Southern California Edison a History, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Performance Appraisal and Deveolpment Guide, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: 1978 Revision: Employee Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Southern California Edison Co. Training Manual for Counter Cashiers, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Retirement Annuity Plan for Employees of Southern California Edison Co. Ltd., Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
    Efective July 1, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Correspondence Concerning Employee Qualification Reports, Publication (Box 106, Folder 15)
    December 14, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 106, Folder: 16 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The S.C.P.E.A. Represents You!, Publication (Box 106, Folder 16)
    July 1952. Item is in English.
- Box: 106, Folder: 17 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor A Vital Part of Management, Publication (Box 106, Folder 17)
    July 15, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Unionization of Foreman, Publication (Box 106, Folder 17)
    July 27, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Facts Cocerning Production, Distribution, Costs, Employees' Earnings and Living Costs in the Bituminous Coal Industry, Publication (Box 106, Folder 17)
    March 10, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Facts Concerning Employees' Earnings, Production and Other Related Data in the Bitumous Coal Industry Vol. 5, Publication (Box 106, Folder 17)
    October 1, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Facts Concerning Employees' Earnings, Cost, Realization and Margin, Production, Distribution and Other Related Data in the Bituminous Coal Industry Vol. 2, Publication (Box 106, Folder 17)
    September 10, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Facts Concerning Employees' Earnings, Cost, Realization and Margin Production, Distribution and Other Related Data in the Bituminous Coal Industry Vol. 3, Publication (Box 106, Folder 17)
    August 10, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Supplement to Book of Facts Published March 10, 1943, Publication (Box 106, Folder 17)
    April 10, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Facts Concerning Employees' Earnings, Cost, Realization and Margin, Production, Distribution and Other Related Data in the Bituminous Coal Industry Vol. 4, Publication (Box 106, Folder 17)
    August 22, 1947. Item is in English.
- Box: 106, Folder: 18 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Your Benefits at Southern New England Telephone, Publication (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Plant Department Working Conditions for Fielf and District Office Employees, Publication (Box 106, Folder 18)
    April 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Southern New England Telephone Co. Wage and Working Practices Binder, Publication (Box 106, Folder 18)
- Box: 106, Folder: 19 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Personnel Handbook, Publication (Box 106, Folder 19)
- Box: 106, Folder: 20 (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Southern Pacific Bulletin, Publication (Box 106, Folder 20)
    July-August, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Southern Pacific Bulletin, Publication (Box 106, Folder 20)
    October, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Southern Pacific Company: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 106, Folder 20)
    December 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Southern Pacific Bulletin, Publication (Box 106, Folder 20)
    July, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A People's Platform for Tansportation, Publication (Box 106, Folder 20)
    By Daniel P. Loomis. October 7, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Southern Pacific News Release, Publication (Box 106, Folder 20)
- Box: 106, Folder: 21 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Wage-Hour Law: promise vs. Performance, Publication (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: The Wage-Hour Law: Promise vs. Performance, Publication (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: A Time Bomb in our Economy, Publication (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: The Perils of Democracy, Publication (Box 106, Folder 21)
    By John H. Kirby. Febrary 19-20, 1918. Item is in English.
- Box: 106, Folder: 22 (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Selling What Railroads Can Produce, Publication (Box 106, Folder 22)
    By D. W. Brosnan. Item is in English.
- Box: 106, Folder: 23 (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Regional Trends from SRC, Publication (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Southern Regional Council 30th Annual Meeting, Publication (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Program and Budget for 1975, Publication (Box 106, Folder 23)
- Box: 106, Folder: 24 (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Your Way to Better Jobs, More Money, Future Security, Publication (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Retirement Income Plan for Spalding Employees, Publication (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Announcement of Group Insurance Plan for New Employees, Publication (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Team Work: The Spalding Platform of Employer-Employee Relationships Including Present Policies and Practices, Publication (Box 106, Folder 24)
- Box: 106, Folder: 25 (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: 50th Anniversary Celebration Tendered to Mr. & Mrs. Jacob Walters, Publication (Box 106, Folder 25)
    May 22, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 107, Folder: 1 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    August 25, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    September 28, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    August 21, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    January 29, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    September 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    Augut 29, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    September 26, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    October 15, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Standard Practice Instructions August 28, 1947, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    October 16, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    November 20, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    November 3, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    October 17, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Weekly Summary of Terminations: Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    September 1, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    January 31, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: General Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    September 23, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    March 21, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Group Accident and Sickness Plan (Weekly Indemnity), Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Group Accident and Sickness Plan (Weekly Indemnity), Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Hospital and Surgical Plan (Blue Cross and Blue Shield), Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Standard Practice Instructions, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    October 28, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Accident Report: to be filled in by injured employee, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Bulletin, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    December 27, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Bulletin, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    November 15, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Bulletin, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    June 25, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Bulletin, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)
    March 13, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Life Insurance Plan: The Sperry Corporation, Publication (Box 107, Folder 1)